retechulous.com 2014-06-26

# Privacy Policy

**What information do we collect?**

We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order or subscribe to our newsletter. 

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address or phone number.

**What do we use your information for?**

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways: 

• To improve our website  
(we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)

• To improve customer service  
(your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)

• To send periodic emails  

> The email address you provide for order processing, may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order, in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, related product or service information, etc.

**How do we protect your information?**

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order

We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required toï¿½keep the information confidential.

After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be kept on file for more than 60 days.

**Do we use cookies?**

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information

We use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart, understand and save your preferences for future visits and keep track of advertisements and .

**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

**Third party links**

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

**Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

**Your Consent**

By using our site, you consent to our [online privacy policy](http://www.freeprivacypolicy.com/).

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page. 

http://retechulous.com/contact  

##  15 Day FREE Trial Membership

You'll have 15 days to access everything in the member's area & see what all the fuss is about. 

If you're not completely convinced that our system will give you huge return on your monthly $97 Investment, you can use the "1 click cancel link" any time during your trial and never pay a dime.

(You can even keep any squeeze pages and leads you generate during your trial -- so there's really no risk here. ) 

After you click "Order" you will have **_instant access_** to everything that's included with membership, free for 15 days.

**If you're thinking - _"$97, That's A Lot Of Money"_** \-- That's because you're probably not used to investing in yourself and your real estate business, (which is probably why you're not at the level you want to be at yet.) 

_Think about it this way._

If you take a totally FREE trial today, and you try just one of the lead generation methods you find inside, is there a chance you'll do at least 1 more transaction as a result? 

Of course there is. And if you stick with us, it's likely you can add 1, 5, or even 10 deals a month to your business, assuming your willing to keep an open mind and take action. 

Go ahead, scroll back up, and start your trial now. 

Charges will appear on your card as ReTechulous.Com.
